http://www.codemicro.com/store/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
CODE Micro does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Your personal information will never be disclosed without your written consent.
At CODE Micro we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience.
When you order from
CODE Micro, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is send to us.
Our site uses "cookies" to keep track of your shopping cart and login status. Our "cookies" do not contain any personally identifying information.
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CODE Micro (see also our
Terms and Conditions of Use). If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Featured Customers
Reviews
I purchased a battery for my Gateway cx2610 laptop from Code Micro.
I was very happy with the produ...Jason G.
Great NorthWeb
Our department needed two discontinued drive modules for our servers. Code Micro delivered on time. ...Mark E.
Citi Corp
Read More ..
Close
